travel-videos.com 2012-02-22

# Tube travel videos, amateur trip videos, travelling movies, europe tripping at Travel-Videos.com

The Travel-videos privacy policy describes how Travel-videos treats personal information when you use the Site services, including information provided when you use Travel-videos.com. In addition, the following describes privacy practices specific to Travel-videos. To understand how we treat the information you give us as you use Travel-videos, you should read this policy.

## Personal Information

  * Non-Account Activity.   You can watch videos on Site without having an Account
  * Account-Related Activity.  Certain other activities on Site -like posting comments or watching certain restricted videos-require you to have an Account. We ask for some personal information when you create an Account, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access.
  * Usage Information.  We may record information about your usage, such as when you use the Site, the channels, groups, and favourites you subscribe to, as well as information you display or click on in the Site (including UI elements, settings, and other information). If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your account.
  * Content Uploaded to Site.  Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, within your playback or profile pages, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.

## Uses

  * If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the Site, we use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Site, as well as provide special personalized features to you.
  * Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you comment videos through the Site and other Users can contact you through comments. Any videos that you submit to the Site may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public.
  * We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Site changes or for customer service purposes).
  * We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous User usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, click stream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the Site and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing User preferences and trends.
  * We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests.
  * To clean all the information the NAI member ad network stores about you for behavioral advertising purposes you can use Opt-out option. You will still get online advertisements but the network from which you opted out will no longer deliver ads tailored to your Web preferences and usage patterns. More detailed here <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

## Your Choices

  * You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through the Site, in which case you can still view videos and explore the Site, but we may not be able to provide certain services to you.

Last updated: April 26th, 2011.
